Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, it's so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in wonderland.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary lives.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
Tsunami!
What is it now?
What's the matter, Luffy?
Maybe it wasn't really such a good idea.
What wasn't a good idea?
I warned him, but he didn't listen.
He said he was so thirsty he
couldn't stand it anymore,
so he chomped down on some of
that cactus growing back there?
to suck out the moisture. Cactus?
Yep, right there.
Those round things.
A tsunami! Ah!
You've got to be kidding!
Those are mezcal cacti!
They're used to make hallucinogenic drugs!
What?
Look out!
We're gonna drown!
Right, bring it on if you got the gun!
I'll beat you all up!
Oh, crap.
Gum-Gum!
Not bad.
Way to go, Chopper.
The operation will begin at the
stroke of noon two days from now.
Have you completed the arrangements?
Yes, everything's in place.
We have 150 billions who
are standing by in Nanohana.
I've also called Mr. Two back here.
It appears that he failed utterly in
his assignment to capture and kill Mr.
Three.
The officer agents have been instructed
to gather tonight at 8 o 'clock.
They're meeting at the Spider's Cafe.
Yes, very good.
It's already past 5 o 'clock.
I would imagine that
the officer agents will
begin gathering at the
cafe any minute now.
Well, well, Merry
Christmas, Merry Christmas!
That was an exhausting trip.
My back is really killing me here.
This is your fault, Mr.
Four.
You're so slow.
If we'd gotten here quicker, my
back wouldn't hurt right now.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
How's business?
He says, Paula, your
place sure is empty today.
It's an empty place.
Place, empty, place, empty, empty.
Well, it is certainly good to see
you again, Miss Merry Christmas.
And you, Mr.
Four, you will have the shop
all to yourselves for a while.
I can go ahead and brew
some tea for you if you
don't mind waiting a few
minutes for it to steep
is it chamomile as
usual mr four no i don't
want to wait for tea i
want something i can drink
right now something fast
right away right away
no waiting right now okay
got it you seem to be in
good spirits is work going
well for you right now
in my line of work if
you don't do well you die
so obviously it's going
well you stupid woman
stupid woman stuman stuman
of course i'll forget
full of me i'm sorry
what is that noise what
kind of crazy singers are
you using in this place
these days idiot singers
no i have a classical
sonata playing right now
there are no words there
shouldn't be any singing
strange
the clouds and
feet on the ground and fly
like a fish in a stream
and spin, just remember, spin, spin,
pretty shoes, and mascara,
pretty shoes and mascara.
I'm such a lovely dancing boy.
Now, we say,
switch foot,
switch foot, and up, and up,
and now, leap away, let's hear
your boys sing it, mascara, and shoes,
hand up, tutu, Ogan's away!
Hello to all and how I do today?
You're a freak!
I am not a freak, Paula.
I am merely a talented
dancer practicing my craft.
I will take one sparkling water, please!
Don't have any.
Don't have any?
Give me a break That's what all
the high-class ballerinas drink
Oh, you're still here You
guys can leave now Right!
And don't forget to practice those
new dance moves like we talked about!
Right!
Unit! Unit! How nice!
The fatty and the old
hag are here with us!
Why don't you just shake your fat mouth,
you weirdo ballet-dancing
swadwearing freak of nature!
Well, nice to see you! Did you hear?
It seems like even Mr.
One's team is being mobilized
for this assignment.
I've never actually had the pleasure
of meeting him and his partner.
I'm really very excited!
There's a little something
I wanted you to have. Here.
Do yourself a favor and hang on to that.
But it's just a scrap of paper.
That paper will reunite us someday.
I'd tuck it away
somewhere for safekeeping.
You don't want it?
No, I do.
It's perfectly natural for a guy to worry.
About his bungling kid brother.
He might be a bit much
for all of you to handle!
But take good care of him for me.
Wait, you're leaving already?
Luffy, when next we meet
we'll both be top pirates
Hey, Luffy, what was that
thing your brother gave you?
I don't really know.
It just looks like a scrap of paper.
It's just paper?
Let me see it.
Well, it looks like it really
is just a piece of paper.
There's nothing written on it or anything.
Is that all really?
I'm not really sure why Ace gave
it to me, but it's important.
Don't eat that!
Don't, camel!
Hey, Luffy, give me your hat.
Why?
If it's really that important to you,
I can sew it to the
underside of your hat ribbon.
Good idea!
Sew it on real good!
Yeah, yeah.
There, it's all done.
Here you go.
Now I don't have to worry about losing it.
Thanks.
If there isn't anything written on it,
what's the point of hanging on to the thing?
Ace said it's important and I should
hang on to it, so I'm hanging on to it.
That's all.
So you're pretty much just
basing your decision on nothing.
No, my instincts, they're right a lot.
As sharp as a tooth.
Will someone please carry me?
moment by moment the night grows later we
are nearing eight o
'clock the appointed time
oh i'm so bored
time to practice my spinning
Oh, what's your problem, you old hag?
Do you want to fight?
Do you really think you could handle me?
Come now, why don't you two cut it out?
Stop fighting.
Hey, what happened to you?
Why are you lying there
on the ground instead
of practicing like you're
supposed to be doing?
We weren't, Talium!
Oh, so these men are
acquaintances of yours.
You see, I found them acting
suspicious out in the desert.
Don't worry, I doubt they'll die.
You seem unnecessarily
concerned about them.
Fostering friendships
will only make you weaker.
Those men of mine, they
don't belong to you!
You better stop, Mr. Two!
Ah! Ah!
Ah!
What the hell?
He flew straight to the wall!
He barely seemed to
notice it was happening!
Do you want to die that badly?
Hold it!
That's enough playing around, Mr.
One.
I'm not done.
Move, Miss Doublefinger.
I still haven't killed him yet.
Stop it!
Come on!
Just get off me, fatty!
Oh, you're killing me!
Mr.
Two, it's time for you
to calm down as well.
It's eight o 'clock.
All the agents that
should be here are here.
What's more, a letter containing the
orders has arrived at the Spider's Cafe.
So, we're instructed to head to
Rainbase, the city of dreams.
In that city we'll meet someone.
A man we know, but whose
face we have never seen.
We're heading to meet the boss.
The officer agent should all be on
their way here to Rain Base as we speak.
I sent bunchy to get them.
I expect them to arrive
sometime later tonight.
To think that you've
actually been Miss Double
Finger this entire time
that's very interesting.
Who knows, perhaps I would have told you,
but none of you ever asked me about it.
The billions that we lost in Nanohana,
have you been able to find replacements?
I've made the assignments
for the replacements.
As far as contacting the new billions,
I've dispatched the lizard
runners to see to that.
Good to hear.
Things are almost ready.
Look up ahead I see a
light does that mean we
made it to Yuba I can't
see with all this sand
blowing everywhere
something here doesn't feel
right there's something
wrong down there I can tell.
Oh no!
The entire city's being
struck by a sandstorm!
Can't be.
It doesn't look good.
This place doesn't look much different
from that Aramalu town from before.
Water!
Vivi, I thought this city was
supposed to be some sort of oasis.
It looks like the oasis has disappeared.
It's been swallowed up by all the sand.
I'm assuming that you're travelers.
You must be exhausted from all
the time spent in that heat!
Sorry, but this town
is a bit dried up too.
It doesn't have much relief to offer.
But still, you're free
to rest here for a while.
We may not have much water.
But there are plenty of
inns here in the town.
It's what we've prided
ourselves so much on after all.
Thank you, but we came here because we
thought the Rebel Army was in this town.
What business do you
have with the Rebel Army?
Curse all of you!
If you're here to join the Rebel Army,
you can just go back where you came from!
If you're looking for those
fools, look elsewhere.
They're no longer in this town.
Wait, they're gone!
They left!
I'm sure you noticed.
The town was just hit by a sandstorm,
but that one certainly wasn't the first.
After three years of no rain, the
land has become increasingly dry.
Sandstorms became a
regular occurrence here.
Little by little,
the oasis that we knew was swallowed up
until the town became what you see now?
a dying wasteland.
With the flow of supplies
to the town Ended the
rebel army couldn't maintain
their Tornado struggle,
so they packed up
They've moved on the rebel
base is now located in Katorea
Um, where's that is
Katorea close to here Vivi?
It's near Nanohana back
the way we came from Well
great coming all this way
was just a waste of time.
Vivi
Wait your names hold on
Luffy.
Princess Vivi, is that really you?
You're alive.
I can't believe it. Thank goodness.
It's me, Vivi.
Don't you recognize me?
I look different.
I lost some weight, I suppose.
Toto, is it really you?
That's right.
It can't be.
So long, my princess.
We won't see you for a while.
As soon as Yuba's up and
running, stop by, princess.
Yes, of course I will, Toto.
Yuba is going to do a great deal
for this dry desert country of ours.
I know it.
Toto that's this guy whatever it's worth
vivi dear i have faith in you and the king
He's a good man a true king who would
never betray his country i know it
This rebellion is ridiculous.
A bunch of faithless fools.
See ya, Vivi.
I hope you grow up to
become a great princess.
We need help.
Our village has dried up.
How can you sit there and do nothing?
Weather is beyond my control as king.
I cannot command nature.
It's beyond any man's power.
There is nothing I can do.
My dad always told me the
king's power is limitless.
He can do anything he wishes.
My abilities exist only
in the realm of men.
I'm not some kind of god.
Your Highness, this boy's
father has come to the palace.
My deepest apologies, Your Majesty.
It's my fault.
Forgive my stupid son, sire.
Place the punishment
for his actions on me.
I'll accept any penalties.
It's my fault, please.
I beg of you.
What were you thinking?
How dare you?
You're stupid.
Insolent.
Thoughtless.
An idiot.
Your name is Toto, is it not?
Yes,
I will officially grant temporary
sanctuary to any villagers
who are suffering due to the
crisis caused by this drought.
You're welcome to live here.
Alubarna is a fine place for
you to plan for your future.
Oh We appreciate your benevolence
keep. Thank you, sire.
Thank you, sir
Whatever I don't want to
live in this stupid capital.
Is that the best you could do for us?
Wait Koza get back here
Mr.
Toto Your son's comments represent
the people's frustrations.
He's a good boy.
He cares for those who suffer.
That is why he is acting in such a way.
Hey there, crybaby?
What did you say to me, midget?
King Cobra
Igaram, what's the matter?
With all due respect, it's unrealistic
to think we can support them all.
Not without exhausting
our funds, sire. Fool!
We will bear the burden of
this crisis with our people.
Their pleas will not be ignored.
I understand.
As you wish.
It's terrible.
Your Majesty, it's Princess Vivi!
I fought with that boy and got beaten.
Vivi!
Princess Vivi!
How dare a commoner lay even a finger
out of the mirror of this esteemed house!
That boy's dead!
No, wait, Igaram, you must calm down!
Your Majesty, my deepest apologies!
Please, sire, kill me instead!
You're both idiots!
You fools!
It was a children's quarrel!
Brute on sale!
Fight!
Punch for the face!
No, she's a princess, Koza!
She's got snotty princess Alesson!
Take her down!
Go, Phoebe!
Shut up, traitors!
Don't you know we're
supposed to cheer for Koza?
I become your leader when I beat you.
That's the deal.
I'd never lose a fight to you, midget.
I've never lost a fight,
especially to a dumb girl.
Is that right?
You can do it, Koza, fight!
Come on, get her!
All right, you guys, listen up.
As of today, Princess Vivi will
be vice leader of the Sansan clan.
Does anyone have a problem with that? No!
Look, Igaram.
Vivi has made some new friends.
Yes, sir.
That is the most important thing to have
if she's to rule Alabasta in my stead.
The people must follow her.
Toto, ma 'am, good morning Where's Leader?
Oh, good morning.
If you're looking for
Koza, he already left.
I assume he's at the usual spot.
See you later.
Hey, Vivi, you coming for lunch?
Yes, please, thank you very much.
What a strange country we live in!
The princess mingling
with commoners like us.
Who would have ever thought?
A sign of peaceful times.
And will you be joining us?
No, no, that's quite all right.
I packed a lunch today.
Your
majesty,
what are you doing here?
Cobra, my lord
I asked you not to follow me again.
Yeah, it's just I wanted to make
sure my precious daughter's okay.
Go home, sire.
I can't babysit you and
Princess Vivi, too. What?
Go home, you heard me.
Hello princess, you lost little
girl, we'll help you out.
Protector sunset clear!
What the hell is wrong with these kids?
They won't give up!
Baby, get going!
We're trying to hold these
guys off when you go!
Baby, get out of here right now!
Yeah, you gotta run now! I can't!
We're not here to kill you,
we just want to kidnap you
for a ransom from your father.
But these other kids...
Damn.
Okay, now just come with
us quietly, Princess Vivi.
Step back!
Protect her to the death, Sand Sand Clan!
You